I think if I didn't do this I would have
to it's like an arrow I don't have many
life life skills when I resume doesn't
look like it probably should I've been
doing this for 20 years but so I think
I'd maybe have to teach just speaking in
front of people part get people to
listen to you I think teaching is harder
than this yeah I mean they that guy
warmed you up and you don't have a
person come in class and start talking
to the kids before you come in there and
make any public or any public y'all have
public schools your public are you
public school 16 well that's where it's
at I'll tell you this if you're a public
school teacher besides being a soldier a
cop or a firefighter you have the
hardest gig in the world man more power
to you because control the puppets
different you want how different it is
dig this I saw my cousin Carl the other
day he is 16 years old he goes to the
largest public high school in the state
of Texas you know what they're serving
in his high school cafeteria Taco Bell
and Subway sandwiches yeah we gaff they
may not see that rectangled pizza with
canned corn on the side every day for 12
years
Pizza and corn pizza and corn they had a
meeting pizza and corn I've been all
around the world you can go seven
continents 200 and some odd countries
walk into any restaurant looking on the
menu and I guarantee you will never see
pizza and corn on the same fiberglass
plate anywhere but public school prison
coincidence hitch our grilled hamburgers
at my high school there was not a grill
within five miles of the high school
cafeteria we had an old lady in the back
with a permanent marker draw a nice row
I just want to know whose idea it was to
send my third grade class to lunch at
9:45 in the day anymore
too early for Pizza Corner yeah you ever
take the public school here in test but
make you go to the media center how's
the library 16 you heard of books you
got books at your school well do we do
dude we call ourselves greatest country
in the world modern-day Roman Empire but
we got kids going through 12 years of
school nowadays getting out and they
can't even read a book that's pretty
heavy they used to make us read they did
you guys remember a thing called the
Weekly Reader book at Pizza Reading
Rainbow highlights all man maybe they're
gods me Margaret super fudge like eight
readers in here to know what I'm talking
about the best part about the Weekly
Reader if you ordered five or more books
you get a free poster too prairie dog
standing off on
appreciate to readers for coming in
public school here in test dude they
make it girl I got to the library and
they'd make it sit in this chair
crossing this angry lady and she puts
headset on her you put a headset on she
makes that machine make that high pitch
he puts a raise your hands full
you're not holding me back I can't even
see you it's not like I'm going off in
the back of my head get me out
it's quarter to ten I gotta go to lunch
it's pizza can't corn today will the
white milk in a nutty buddy if I were a
rapper my name would be white milk
DJ nutty buddy
do school functions hey everybody Mike
spielberg thanks for watching that small
clip of my special you can watch my
entire special for 99 cents just by
clicking right here or you can watch
more clips by clicking right here or you
can subscribe either way you've got to
click something or I'm gonna sit here
with this strange mustache and stare
through this computer screen until you
decide you're gonna click something I
got all the time in the world I don't
have a day job so do ahead and click
something already click it you know you
want to click something